Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/leslie-correa-543545a1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Chatbot Development
Microsoft Bot Framework
Amazon Lex

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)
Kannada (Professional Working)
Tulu (Native or Bilingual)
Konkani (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

AWS INNOVATE ONLINE CONFERENCE 2019

Al Pair Programming with GitHub Copilot

AWSOME DAY ONLINE CONFERENCE

RPA Developer

Introduction to Voice Design with Amazon's Alexa

Honors-Awards

Spot award

EVRY Elite Club member 2019 - 2020

Leslie Correa

Conversational Al Specialist | NLP | Chatbot Developer | Microsoft Bot Framework | AWS LEX | Google Dialogflow | Mobile Developer Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Passionate Conversational AI Specialist and Chatbot Developer with good knowledge in areas like Microsoft Bot Framework, AWS LEX, and Google Dialogflow also a Mobile Developer with Android, iOS, and Xamarin development skills. Team player with good communication, analytical, and programming skills. Open source contributor at GitHub and Stackoverflow.

Experience

EVRY India

Software Engineer

September 2017 - May 2022 (4 years 9 months)

Bangalore

Chatbot Developer | Microsoft Bot Framework | AWS LEX | Google Dialogflow | Mobile Developer

SPAN Infotech

Software Engineer

August 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 7 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Mobile developer(Android, Xamarin Forms and Xamarin android)

Education

Mangalore Institute of Technology and Engineering, MITE Engineer's Degree, EC · (2010 - 2014)